export const popQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which of Katy Perry’s albums has been her most successful?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Her", "Teenage Dream", "California Girls", "Katy"],
      correct: "Teenage Dream",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which musician was known as the “King of Pop”?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Michael Jackson", "Chris Brown", "Usher Raymond", "Justin Beiber"],
      correct: "Michael Jackson",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What film did the phrase “I see dead people” come from?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Scream", "Scary Movie", "Sixth Sense", "Sixteen Candles"],
      correct: "Sixth Sense",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "In what year was YouTube created?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["2003", "2001", "2004", "2005"],
      correct: "2005",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "The hit singles I Just Can’t Stop Loving You and The Man in the Mirror appeared on which Michael Jackson album?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Off The Wall", "Bad", "Dangerous", "Thriller"],
      correct: "Bad",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Cyndi Lauper is famous for what Tony award winning musical?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "Kinky Boots", "Time After Time", "Memories"],
      correct: "Kinky Boots",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the most awarded diamond artist?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Bruno Mars", "Michael Jackson", "The Beatles", "Celine Dion"],
      correct: "Bruno Mars",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "In this hit Beyonce was 'Drunk In Love' riding on what object?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Wood", "Six-Fours", "Surfboard", "Watermelon"],
      correct: "Surfboard",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "'Now That's What I Call...' made compilation albums in all genres except? ",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Club Hits", "Love", "R&B", "Hip-Hop"],
      correct: "Hip-Hop",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Justin Beiber got famous on this platform. However, he was the first?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Drake", "Druski", "Soulja Boy", "2Chainz"],
      correct: "Soulja Boy",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Pharrell produced one of these Britney Spears Hit. Which one?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Girls", "I'm a Slave 4 U", "Dirty", "Genie In A Bottle"],
      correct: "I'm a Slave 4 U",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Wham!'s George Michael sang 'Wake Me Up Before You'?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Leave", "Stay", "Go", "Breathe"],
      correct: "Go",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Whitney Houston's most recent GRAMMY win belongs to which song?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["I Wanna Dance With Somebody", "It's Not Right But It's Okay", "I Look To You", "Heartbreak Hotel"],
      correct: "It's Not Right But It's Okay",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Who encouraged the world to ‘Get Down on It’ in 1981?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["The Warriors", "The Sugarhill Gang", "Kool and the Gang", "The Furious Five"],
      correct: "Kool and the Gang",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Michael Jackson debuted his trademark moonwalk during which song in 1983?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Bad", "Beat It", "Thriller", "Billie Jean"],
      correct: "Billie Jean",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which female singer won a grammy for best new artist in 1985? ",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Cyndi Lauper", "Madonna", "Whitney Houston", "Beyonce"],
      correct: "Cyndi Lauper",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which 90's girl group is the second best-selling in history after the Spice Girls? ",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Spice Girls", "SWV", "Xscape", "TLC"],
      correct: "TLC",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "It took Mariah Carey __ minutes to write holiday hit 'All I Want for Christmas is You' in 1994?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["10", "20", "15", "5"],
      correct: "15",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What was, by a considerable margin, the best-selling single of the 90s?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Candle in the Wind (Elton John)", "Doo-Wop (Lauryn Hill)", "Beat It (Michael Jackson)", "Bills, BIlls, Bills (Destiny Child)"],
      correct: "Candle in the Wind (Elton John)",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "The most awarded female act of all time goes to… which 80s sensation?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Madonna", "Whitney Houston", "Beyonce", "Adele"],
      correct: "Whitney Houston",
    },
  },
];
